<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pet Map</string>
    <string name="action_add_sample">Add Sample Pets</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pet_details">Pet Details </string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "This Here contains details about the Pet.\n\n"

        "Tinker is a Rat Terrier or Toy Fox Terrier Mix, female. She was born approximately in January 2006."
        "She weighs 8 lbs. She is crate trained.\n\n"
        "She’s very affectionate and outgoing, except when it comes to being picked up or walking on a leash.\n"
        "Currently any situation that calls for her to do either is extremely stressful for her, so training classes will be required for Tinker in her new home."
        "Compatibility with other dogs depends mostly on their size. Cat compatibility is still being evaluated.\n\n\n"
        "Their Adoption Process\n"
        "Additional Adoption Info\n\n"
        "First, decide on the kind of dog or cat you want (large, small, active, older, puppy, kitten, long hair, short hair, etc.) and find a few pets that fit your criteria on our web site.\n"

        "Then either contact the foster home directly or visit us at our weekly pet fairs.\n"

        "Next a NARF representative will conduct an interview to make sure that the pet of your choice is a good match.\n"

        "The donation for dogs ranges from $200 – $300, and $120 for cats. This donation covers the cost of spaying or neutering, vaccinations, and microchipping. In some cases, a training contract may be required for our dogs with an additional deposit.\n\n"
        "Go Meet Their Pets\n"
        "Check out our events page for upcoming events and pet fairs: http://www.narfrescue.org/events/"
        "More About This Rescue"
        "The Nike Animal Rescue Foundation (NARF) is a non-profit, all volunteer organization founded in 1985 in San Jose, California."
        "NARF is dedicated to protecting dogs and cats. We strive to eliminate animal overpopulation through spay and neuter programs and public education."
        "Our volunteers rescue and shelter cats and dogs in need. We provide medical care and locate quality, permanent homes for these animals. We are also a NO KILL shelter."
        "The animals are fostered in our volunteer’s home; allowing us to give adopters a more complete background about their personality and how they get along with other animals, children, etc."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_pet"></string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="action_delete_sample">Delete All Pet Data</string>
    <string name="editor_activity_title_new_pet">Add a Pet</string>

    <!-- Label for editor menu option to save pet and leave editor [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="action_save">Save</string>

    <!-- Label for editor overflow menu option that deletes the current pet [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="action_delete">Delete</string>

    <!-- Label for overview category of attributes in the editor [CHAR LIMIT=30] -->
    <string name="category_overview">Overview</string>

    <!-- Label for gender information in the editor [CHAR LIMIT=30] -->
    <string name="category_gender">Gender</string>

    <!-- Label for measurement information in the editor [CHAR LIMIT=30] -->
    <string name="category_measurement">Measurement</string>

    <!-- Text hint for name field in the editor [CHAR LIMIT=30] -->
    <string name="hint_pet_name">Name</string>

    <!-- Text hint for breed field in the editor [CHAR LIMIT=30] -->
    <string name="hint_pet_breed">Breed</string>

    <!-- Text hint for name field in the editor [CHAR LIMIT=30] -->
    <string name="hint_pet_weight">Weight</string>

    <!-- Units for weight of the pet (kilograms) [CHAR LIMIT=5] -->
    <string name="unit_pet_weight">kg</string>

    <!-- Label for dropdown menu option if the pet's gender is unknown [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="gender_unknown">Unknown</string>

    <!-- Label for dropdown menu option if the pet is male [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="gender_male">Male</string>

    <!-- Label for dropdown menu option if the pet is female [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="gender_female">Female</string>
    <string name="title_activity_editor">Add a new pet</string>
</resources>
